https://www.sc.edu/about/notices/privacy/

Skip to Content
StudyAcademic OverviewUndergraduate EducationGraduate EducationProfessional ProgramsContinuing EducationOnline EducationAcademic CalendarAcademic BulletinsMajors and Degrees at South CarolinaAccountingAdvertisingAfrican American StudiesAnthropologyArt EducationArt HistoryArt StudioAthletic TrainingBiochemistry and Molecular BiologyBiological SciencesBiomedical SciencesBiostatisticsBusiness AdministrationCardiovascular TechnologyChemistryChinese StudiesClassicsCommunication Sciences and DisordersComparative LiteratureComputer Science / Computer EngineeringCounseling / Counselor EducationCreative WritingCriminology and Criminal JusticeDanceEconomicsEducation: Curriculum and InstructionEducation: Early Childhood EducationEducation: Elementary EducationEducation: Language and LiteracyEducation: Middle Level EducationEducation: Physical EducationEducation: Secondary EducationEducation: Special EducationEducation: Teacher EducationEducational Administration and Higher EducationEducational Psychology and ResearchEducational TechnologyEngineering: Aerospace EngineeringEngineering: Biomedical EngineeringEngineering: Chemical EngineeringEngineering: Civil EngineeringEngineering: Electrical EngineeringEngineering: Engineering ManagementEngineering: Mechanical EngineeringEngineering: Nuclear EngineeringEnglishEnvironmental Health SciencesEnvironmental Science / Environmental StudiesEpidemiologyEuropean StudiesExercise ScienceFilm and Media StudiesFinanceForeign LanguageFrenchGeographyGeological SciencesGeophysicsGermanGlobal Supply Chain and Operations ManagementHealth CommunicationHealth Information TechnologyHealth Promotion, Education and BehaviorHealth Services Policy and ManagementHistoryHospitality ManagementHuman ResourcesInformation ScienceIntegrated Information TechnologyInterdisciplinary StudiesInternational BusinessInternational StudiesJournalismLatin American StudiesLawLiberal StudiesLibrary and Information ScienceLinguisticsManagementMarine ScienceMarketingMathematicsMedia ArtsMedicineMusicMusic: ConductingMusic: Jazz StudiesMusic: Music CompositionMusic: Music EducationMusic: Music HistoryMusic: Music PerformanceMusic: Music Pedagogy (Piano / Violin)Music: Music TheoryMusic: Opera TheatreNursingOrganizational LeadershipPharmacyPhilosophyPhysicsPolitical ScienceProfessional Science MasterPsychologyPublic AdministrationPublic HealthPublic RelationsReal EstateReligious StudiesRetailingRisk Management and InsuranceRussianSocial WorkSociologySpanishSpeech / Language PathologySport and Entertainment ManagementStatisticsTheatreTourism ManagementVisual CommunicationsWomen's and Gender StudiesGlobal StudiesMass Communications at South CarolinaPhysical Therapy at South CarolinaColleges and SchoolsCollege of Arts and SciencesDarla Moore School of BusinessCollege of EducationCollege of Engineering and ComputingThe Graduate SchoolCollege of Hospitality, Retail and Sport ManagementSchool of LawCollege of Information and CommunicationsSchool of Medicine ColumbiaSchool of Medicine GreenvilleSchool of MusicCollege of NursingCollege of PharmacyArnold School of Public HealthCollege of Social WorkSouth Carolina Honors CollegeResearch OpportunitiesUndergraduate ResearchDiscoverMagellan ScholarsDiscovery DayGraduate ResearchAcademic Success ResourcesCareer PreparationLibraries and CollectionsThomas Cooper LibraryDigital CollectionsEducational Film CollectionElliot White Springs Business LibraryKaresh Law LibraryLibrary Annex and Conservation FacilityMusic LibraryMoving Images Research CollectionsIrvin Department of Rare Books and Special CollectionsSchool of Medicine LibrarySouth Carolina Political CollectionsSouth Caroliniana LibraryExperienceLiving HereGet InvolvedGrab a BiteCampus Restaurants ListSee the WorldCatch a ShowGet in the GameVisitVirtual and Campus VisitsVirtual TourCampus MapExplore ColumbiaAccommodationsApplyUndergraduate AdmissionsGraduate School AdmissionsProfessional School AdmissionsCost, Tuition and Financial AidResearchResearch Focus AreasHealth SciencesAdvanced MaterialsEnergyEnvironment and SustainabilityFaculty ExpertiseBusiness Partnership OpportunitiesFacilities and ResourcesAboutSouth Carolina at a GlanceOur MissionOur LeadershipMeet Our PresidentPresidential CommunicationsShare Your ThoughtsRequest for RemarksBoard of TrusteesUniversity OfficialsOffices and DivisionsSignature EventsUofSC WelcomeConvocationConvocation RSVPFamily WeekendUofSC HomecomingMLK CelebrationCommencementOur HistoryDirectory SearchEmployment: Working at UofSCBenefitsNews & EventsOur StoriesUniversity EventsAthletics
Tools & Resources
Calendar
Map
Directory
Give
Student Gateway
Faculty & Staff Gateway
Parents & Families Gateway
This Privacy Statement governs the manner in which the University of South Carolina
collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a
“User”) of the sc.edu website (“Site”). This privacy statement applies to the Site and all products and
services offered by University of South Carolina.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways,
including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe
to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other
activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may
be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number.
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification
information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users
can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it
may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact
with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name,
the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to
our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized
and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. A User’s Web browser places
cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information
about them. Users may choose to set their Web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert
them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site
may not function properly.
How we use collected information
University of South Carolina may collect and use Users personal information for the
following purposes:
To provide services to the Carolina community and to serve other University needs
To improve constituent service
Information you provide helps us respond to your constituent service requests and
support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use
the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of
interest to them.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may
include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at
any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include
detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security
measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction
of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data
stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.
We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal
identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners,
trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third
party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer
activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share
your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that
you have given us your permission. Laws do exist in the State of South Carolina to
ensure government is open and that the public has a right to access appropriate records
and information possessed by a government agency. At the same time, however, there
are exceptions to the public’s right to access certain records in order to protect
against the unreasonable invasion of personal privacy of individuals. Such exceptions
are authorized by both State and Federal law. Information collected from users of
this Site, similarly to information collected during in-person visits to a government
office, may be subject to inspection and copying by the public, unless an exemption
exists in law. In the event there is a conflict between this Privacy Statement and
a State or Federal law governing the disclosure of public records, the applicable
law shall control. The Family Privacy Protection Act of 2002 prohibits persons or
private entities from using personal information obtained from State agencies for
commercial solicitation purposes. A person knowingly violating this prohibition is
guilty of a misdemeanor and subject to the penalties specified in S.C. Code Ann. Section
30-2-50(D).
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and
services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third
parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are
not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site.
In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly
changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and constituent
service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites
which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy statement
University of South Carolina has the discretion to update this privacy statement at
any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.
We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed
about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge
and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy statement periodically
and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this statement and terms of service.
If you do not agree to this, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the
Site following the posting of changes to this statement will be deemed your acceptance
of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site,
or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Communications and Public AffairsUniversity of South Carolina
920 Sumter StreetColumbia, SC 29208
803-777-8161
webcomm@sc.edu
This document was last updated on September 3, 2013.
©
